Thimira Samarakoon

thimirasamarakoon.github.io thimiransamarakoon@gmail.com +94773355731

Profile

I like to call myself an interaction enthusiast. I believe Paul Rand when he said 'Design is Everything'. To add to that, I believe an experience provides by a well thought out Design means everything. I'm a fan of simplicity within user centered design and

I'm a fan of simplicity within user centered design and modern design and innovation.

Experience

Shift Solutions Brand Strategy and Planning intern

Worked integrating with brands team and creative team to come up with suitable strategies for varies client brands.

Jan 2020 - May 2020.

Freelance Designer

I designed logos, brand guides, and social media contents for multiple clients by working remotely for various clients. and i did some projects as a video editor. 2019 - Present

Event Organized and Volunteered

DesignCode 2017 & 2018 Typoday 2017,2018 & 2019 ATypl 2019

ki	ш	
NI	LL	3

User Research Journey Mapping Wireframing Prototyping User Testing Evaluating Visual Software Adobe Suite Figma Figma DaVinci Resolve

Research

Suitability of a framework design for 'design alternative' stage in interaction design process through 'scene triangle' in storytelling.

-As a Dissertation

Exploration of adapting 'temporal setting' narrative element to develop an effective interaction method to increase the quality of the entertainment experience in interactive cinema.

-As a Comprehensive Study for a Comprehensive Design Project.

Education

University of Moratuwa Class of 2020

Bachelor of Design (Hons.)
Specializing in Media and Communication Design